{
    "id": "cf3790162f76464f80e6676aaed46233",
    "title": "Modal Auxiliaries",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………………… you work this sum?",
            "description": "Can expresses ability.",
            "answers": [
                "Can",
                "Will",
                "May"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………… lift this box.",
            "description": "Cannot expresses inability.",
            "answers": [
                "cannot",
                "may not",
                "shall not"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………………. be at home now.",
            "description": "May expresses possibility in affirmative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "can",
                "may",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………… it be a dog?",
            "description": "Can expresses possibility in questions and negative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "May",
                "Will",
                "Can"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "No. It ……………………….. be a tiger.",
            "description": "Can expresses possibility in questions and negative sentences.",
            "answers": [
                "may not",
                "cannot",
                "will not"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………….. run miles when I was young.",
            "description": "Could shows past ability.",
            "answers": [
                "could",
                "might",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that I …………………………… go home.",
            "description": "Both could and might can indicate permission.",
            "answers": [
                "could",
                "might",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………. not enter my house again.",
            "description": "With second and third person pronouns shall can be used to express a command or threat.",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "would",
                "could"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ……………………………. not permit this.",
            "description": "Will indicates determination.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "will",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………….. sit for hours listening to the radio.",
            "description": "We can use will to express characteristic habit.",
            "answers": [
                "shall",
                "will",
                "may"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………………….. you lend me your pen?",
            "description": "Will is often used in polite requests.",
            "answers": [
                "Will",
                "Shall",
                "Should"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She said she ………………………. buy me drinks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "would",
                "shall"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}